(& opam env) -split '\r?\n' | ForEach-Object { Invoke-Expression $_ }

(*
Context: We are all one, just separate instances of the same source. To hurt someone, is to hurt oneself.
When people are cruel, they hurt themselves. Kindness bears miracles for others, the life that is oneself.
To be kind is hard, to be cruel, less so. Let us endeavor so that ourselves shall prosper. We are all but one.
*)